Finding Aid for the John Cope Caldwell Papers MSS.0066
Vanderbilt University Special Collections
- Correspondence - Incoming (Box 4)
  - Gronenberg, Rubert H., to John Day (1), Feb. 6, 1951
  - Grossman, Frances, to Richard J. Walsh, Jr. (1), Nov. 12, 1958
  - Gruver, Kate E. (3), Mar. 9, 1956, Apr. 19, 1956, Feb. 26, 1957
  - Gunn, Henry M. (1), Sept. 5, 1957
  - Gutke, Audrey (1), June 5, 1959
  - Hagan, Dorothy S. (1), Jan. 8, 1958
  - Halden, Frahk C. (1), Apr. 27, 1954
  - Hall, Clarence W. (15), Aug. 6, 1953, Aug. 11, 1953, Aug. 14, 1953, Nov. 16, 1953, Oct. 21, 1955, Mar. 20, 1956, May 2, 1956, Oct. 3, 1956, Nov. 1, 1956, Dec. 7, 1956, Dec. 14, 1956, Feb. 13, 1957, Mar. 4, 1957, Jan. 20, 1958, Jan. 20, 1958
  - Hall, Mary (1), Aug. 24, 1965
  - Halsted, Linda (1), Oct. 29, 1958
  - Hamill, Francis J., to Enoch-Pratt Free Library (1), May 11, 1955
  - Hamill, Francis J. (1), May 11, 1955
  - Hamilton, M. C. (1), Aug. 10, 1955
  - Han, Shin Tino (1), Aug. 8, 1957
  - Han, Pyo Wook (2), May 23, 1956, Feb. 3, 1959
  - Hansen, Hoppy (1), Feb. 14, 1959
  - Hansen, I. Carl, to Janet Schoelles (1), Dec. 11, 1952
  - Hag, S. M. (7), Apr. 3, 1959, Apr. 15, 1959, May 13, 1959, July 21, 1959, Sept. 30, 1959, Oct. 28, 1959, Feb. 23, 1960
  - Harris, M. S. (1), Oct. 7, 1959
  - Hart, Lois (1), Sept. 21, 1962
  - Hart, Pat (1), Oct. 10, 1966
  - Hartley, R. P. (1), Apr. 8, 1958
  - Hartman, Rachal (1), July 19, 1955
  - Harvey, Paul (1), Jan. 5, 1953
  - Harza, L. F. (2), Mar. 21, 1952, May 12, 1952
  - Hellberg, Charlotte S. (1), Oct. 13, 1960
  - Hemphill, R. W., to Haller Lewis (1), July 13, 1959
  - Hendrix, Fredrik (1)
  - Hendry, John L. (2), Oct. 11, 1965, Jan. 18, 1966
  - Henle, R. J. (2), Aug. 5, 1957, July 15, 1958
  - Heppell, M. E. (1), Dec. 20, 1963
  - Herald, Christian (2), Nov. 17, 1953, July 15, 1955
  - Hermann, Harold L. (6), Aug. 31, 1954, Mar. 28, 1958, Oct. 31, 1958, Nov. 18, 1958, Nov. 24, 1958, Jan. 13, 1959
  - Hess, Eric H. J. (2), Dec. 3, 1960, Jan. 13, 1961
  - Hess, Karl (3), Apr. 14, 1954, May 7, 1954, May 10, 1954
  - Hibbs, Ben, to Daniel A. Poling (1), Nov. 9, 1954
  - Hickson, Oswald, to Reader's Digest Company (1), July 18, 1958
  - Hickson, Oswald (1), June 30, 1958
  - High, Stanley, to Clarence Hall (1), June 14, 1956
  - High, Stanley (4), July 31, 1956, Aug. 8, 1956, Nov. 1, 1956, Dec. 4, 1956
  - Hill, Harold E., to Roy S. Buffet, Harvey L. Long, and Robert L. Floyd (3), July 29, 1952, Aug. 13, 1952, Aug. 15, 1952
  - Hill, Harold E. (3), July 11, 1952, Aug. 5, 1952, Aug. 20, 1952
  - Hill, Robert W. (4), Dec. 13, 1961, Dec. 13, 1961, Sept. 13, 1963, Sept. 24, 1963
  - Hinchey, C. E. (1), Aug. 13, 1957
  - Hiscock, Ira, V., to John T. Gibson (1), Mar. 11, 1957
  - Hitching, R. (1), Oct. 20, 1957
  - Holland, Kate.R. (1), Feb. 11, 1957
  - Holmes, Sam (1), Mar. 17, 1959
  - Hong, W. (1), Apr. 12, 1951
  - Hoppe, Clemens B. (1), Aug. 13, 1959
  - Hornbeck, Standley K., to Marvin Liebman (1), Nov. 30, 1959
  - Horovitz, Eva (2), Aug. 30, 1962, Sept. 12, 1962
  - Horrigan, Mary (1), Apr. 13, 1955
  - Horton, Philip (5), Jan. 3, 1951, July 20, 1951, Aug. 6, 1951, Mar. 28, 1952, Apr. 7, 1952
  - House, C. C. (1), June 29, 1960
  - Howe, Harold C. (14), Feb. 27, 1958, June 26, 1958, Nov. 7, 1958, Nov. 24, 1958, Feb. 10, 1959, Apr. 14, 1959, May 12, 1959, Aug. 31, 1959, Oct. 30, 1959, Mar. 14, 1960, Sept. 26, 1960, n.d., n.d., n.d.
  - Howe, Quincey (3), Mar. 15, 1952, May 29, 1952, June 2, 1952
  - Hoy, Billie A,, to J. C. Clarke (1), Dec. 26, 1957
  - Hsin-min, Chu (2), Jan. 8, 1955, Oct. 9, 1955
  - Humbert, Russell J., to Elizabeth Schenk (1), Oct. 25, 1951
  - Humbert, Russell J. (1), Oct. 27, 1951
  - Hunter, Edward (1), July 9, 1957
  - Hunter, Vallie H., to Forrest F. Reed (1), Jan. 18, 1955
  - Huntley, F. A., to George F. Johnston (1), Aug. 19, 1956
  - Huntley, F. A. (1), July 23, 1956
  - Hurleigh, Robert F. (2), Mar. 29, 1955, Apr. 7, 1955
  - Hutchinson, Colleen (1), Feb. 14, 1964
  - Ifeagwu, C. O. (2), Mar. 20, 1958, Mar. 22, 1958
  - Ingram, Jeannie (1), Aug. 4, 1965
  - Iwata, K., to Richard J. Walsh (1), Aug. 10, 1959
  - Jackson, Alice W. (3), Feb. 2, 1963, n.d., n.d.
    6
  - Jackson, Pricilla (1), Apr. 27, 1955
  - James, Ralph (1), Feb. 6, 1964
  - Jamison, David (1), Apr. 15-, 1955
  - Jaskieviez, W. C. (3), Nov. 15, 1955, Apr. 6, 1956, Nov. 2, 1956
  - Jennings, Rachel (1), Jan. 23, 1963
  - Jennings, Roy E., to Elizabeth Schenk (1), Oct. 23, 1952
  - Jennings, Roy E. (2), June 26, 1952, Nov. 5, 1952
  - Jessup, John K., to Lee Keedick (1), June 8, 1955
  - Johnson, Robert L., to Richard J. Walsh, Jr. (2), Jan. 18, 1956
  - Johnson, William R. (1), Mar. 1, 1952
  - Johnston, Abigail (8), July 3, 1962, July 16, 1962, July 25, 1962, Aug. 1, 1962, Aug. 2, 1962, Sept. 12, 1962, Sept. 21, 1962, Nov. 8, 1962
  - Johnston, George F. ,to Robert T. Oliver, Syngman Rhee, Robert Kane, George Masters, Marvin Plake, J. Calvitt Clarke, L. E. Skinner, and Ralph L. Boyce (10), Oct. 25, 1955, Nov. 10, 1955, Jan. 18, 1956, Apr. 6, 1956, Apr. 17, 1956, May 21, 1956, May 23, 1956, May 25, 1956, Sept. 4, 1956, Sept. 28, 1956
  - Johnston, George F. (22), 1954-1961
    Dates of letters: Dec. 30, 1954, July 19, 1955, Nov. 2, 1955, Feb 13, 1956, Feb. 20, 1956, Mar. 6, 1956, Apr. 6, 1956, May 21, 1956, July 24, 1956, Aug. 13, 1956, Sept. 4, 1956, Sept.28, 1956, Mar. 22, 1957, June 20, 1957, Jan. 27, 1959, Jan. 30, 1959, Feb. 9, 1959, Mar. 18, 1959, Apr. 21, 1959, Apr. 4, 1960, Jan. 3, 1961, n.d. n.d.
  - Johnston, Shirley L. (1), July 9, 1959
  - Jonas, Gilbert, to George F. Johnston (1), Oct. 8, 1956
  - Jones, Betty (1), Oct. 1, 1963
  - Jones, Carl A., to Ralph Wheatley (1), June 21, 1954
  - Jones, Carl A. (1), June 16, 1954
  - Jones, Lucile W. (1), Feb. 3, 1959
  - Jones, W. Jackson (5), Sept. 13, 1956, Oct. 1, 1956, Oct. 4, 1956, Dec. 3 1956, Jan. 3, 1957
  - Jones, Winona S. (2), Jan. 23, 1954, Dec. 30, 1954
  - Joray, Juliette P. (1), Aug. 22, 1956
  - Kai-shek, Chiang (2), June 28, 1955, Apr. 8, 1957
  - Kaltenborn, H. V. (2), Oct. 16, 1952, Feb. 25, 1955
  - Kan, E. (1), Mar. 11, 1963
  - Kane, Harnett T. (2), Nov. 30, 1957, n.d.
  - Kassube, William F. (1), Aug. 10, 1953
  - Katgard, A. J. (5), Sept. 28, 1959, Feb. 2, 1960, Feb. 9, 1961, July 20, 1965, Feb. 22, 1966
  - Kavanaugh, Dorothy (2), June 29, 1955, Feb. 10, 1959
  - Keedick, Lee (23), 1951-1960
    Dates of letters: June 15, 1951, Nov. 9, 1951, Sept. 26, 1952, Oct. 29, 1952, Nov. 5, 1952, Dec. 10, 1952, Mar. 5, 1953, Mar. 9, 1953, May 3, 1954, Mar. 30, 1955, Mar. 21, 1956, Jan. 29, 1957, Feb. 14, 1957, Oct. 16, 1957, July 24, 1958, Apr. 22, 1959, Apr. 12, 1960, May 20, 1959, Oct. 14, 1959, Oct. 28, 1960, Nov. 22, 1960, n.d., n.d.
  - Keedick, Robert, to John Jessup, North Callahan, Brigham Day, Daniel A. Poling, and Frederic Graeser (6), Apr. 15, 1955, Mar. 22, 1956, June 24, 1955, July 6, 1955, July 19, 1955, Dec. 18, 1956
  - Keedick, Robert (49), 1951-1960
    Dates of letters: Feb. 23, 1951, Mar. 12, 1951, Mar. 14, 1951, Mar. 14, 1951, Mar. 17, 1951, Mar. 19, 1951, Mar. 21, 1951, Mar. 26, 1951, Apr. 5, 1951, Apr. 6, 1951, Apr. 6, 1951, Apr. 11, 1951, Apr. 18, 1951, May 2, 1951, May 31, 1951, Oct. 16, 1954, Oct. 22, 1954, Feb. 10, 1955, Feb. 18, 1955, Mar. 10, 1955, Mar. 30, 1955, Apr. 26, 1955, May 17, 1955, May 27, 1955, June 10, 1955, June 22, 1955, June 24, 1955, July 6, 1955, July 12, 1955, July 26, 1955, Aug. 5, 1955, Aug. 11, 1955, Aug. 12, 1955, Aug. 18, 1955, Oct. 26, 1955, Nov. 1, 1955, Nov. 29, 1955, Feb. 2, 1956, Jan. 28, 1957, Jan. 30, 1957, Sept. 25, 1958, June 2, 1958, June 24, 1958, Mar. 12, 1959, Mar. 26, 1959, Apr. 8, 1959, July 29, 1959, Aug. 27, 1959, May 27, 1960, June 3, 1960, June 30, 1960, Dec. 5, 1960, n.d.
  - Keeley, Joseph C., to Robert Keedick (1), Dec. 30, 1955
  - Keeley, Joseph C. (11), Sept. 29, 1953, Jan. 13, 1954, Jan. 18, 1954, Jan. 27, 1954, Feb. 18, 1954, Apr. 19, 1954, May 24, 1954, July 13, 1954, Jan. 4, 1955, Oct. 4, 1955, Nov. 10, 1955
  - Kefauver, Estes (1), May 12, 1950
  - Keller, Mary F. (2), Mar. 5, 1954, Mar. 30, 1954
  - Kent, Steven (1), n.d.
  - Kepple, Ella H. (1), Sept. 26, 1962
  - Kharas, R. K. (1), Oct. 19, 1959
  - Kira, Slim (1), Nov. 23, 1953
  - King,' ?, to Larry ? (1), Mar. 14, 1952
  - Kingshill, Howard J. (1), n.d.
  - Kirk, Helen S., to Elizabeth Schenk (1), May 3, 1954
  - Kirk, Russell, to Richard Walsh, Jr. (1), Feb. 15, 1956
  - Kirk, Russell (2), June 1, 1955, Sept. 1, 1955
  - Kirkland, H. Burnham (1), June 29, 1955
  - Klein, Audrey (1), Apr. 11, 1962
  - Klein, S. (1), n.d.
  - Kloneker, A. (1), Jan. 7, 1959
  - Klopp, Henry (1), July 25, 1960
  - Kneebone, Edith (1), n.d.
  - Knight, Nancy, to Ted Brown (1), June 10, 1965
  - Knoles, Mildred R. (2), Feb. 23, 1956, Mar. 7, 1956
  - Knudsen, Joyce, to J. Calvitt Clarke (1), Aug. 6, 1956
  - Koehler, Norman E., to John Day Company (1), Nov.l, 1960
  - Kofod, Leon V. (1), Apr. 17, 1958
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, to Henry Regnery and Roy Cohn (2), Aug. 1, 1952, June 22, 1953
  - Kohlberg, Alfred (11), Sept. 18, 1952, May 29, 1953, June 16, 1953, June 22, 1953, June 25, li53, Nov. 9, 1953, Nov. 16, 1953, Dec. 23, 1954, May 10, 1955, Feb. 27, 1956, Feb. 10, 1958
  - Kopacz, Sandra (3), Aug. 31, 1964, Mar. 3, 1965, June 15, 1965
  - Korell, Marguerite C., to Marjorie L. Daniel (1), Feb. 24, 1955
  - Korell, Marguerite C. (10), Aug. 19, 1954, Oct. 23, 1954, Dec. 1, 1954, Jan. 12, 1955, Feb. 23, 1955, Mar. 18, 1955, Apr. 28, 1955, June 21, 1955, Aug. 5, 1955, Aug, 17, 1955
  - Kornhoff, Roberta (1), n.d.
  - Kritzky, Stuart, to William F. Strube (1), Aug. 23, 1952
  - Kruger, Karl K. (1), Mar. 4, 1954
  - Kummerly (1), Jan. 11, 1962
  - Kupitz, Sybille (1), Dec. 26, 1962
  - Lacy, Birdie May (1), Oct. 1, 1952
  - Lacy, William I. (1), Aug. 28, 1951
  - Lady, Harold W. (2), June 8, 1954, Nov. 5, 1955
  - La Follette, Sdzanne (3), Oct. 11, 1955, Oct. 31, 1955, Nov, 29, 1955
  - Lai, Ho Shai (2), Apr. 10, 1956, Oct. 16, 1956
  - Laidley, Mary (1), Mar. 19, 1958
  - La Liberte, Patricia (1), July 9, 1952
  - Lancaster, Luis H. (1), Sept. 17, 1959
  - Lancaster, W. H. (1), Sept. 23, 1952
  - Landress, Sylvia (1), Sept. 11, 1957
  - Langstaff, George (1), Nov. 20, 1952
  - Larkin, Fred S. (1), Feb. 21, 1955
  - Larson, Arthur (1), Dec. 7, 1956
  - Lasky, Victor (3), Mar. 23, 1953, June 24, 1953, n.d.
  - Lau, Allen (4), Mar. 21, 1955, Mar. 30, 1955, July 11, 1955, Mar. 5, 1958
  - Laymon, H. K. (2), Apr. 14, 1955, Nov. 30, 1955
  - Leek, ? (2), Mar. 4, 1958, Oct. 1, 1960
  - Lee, Charles E. (2), May 7, 1957, July 18, 1957
  - Lee, E. Yian (1), Aug. 29, 1958
  - Lee, Soo Uoung (1), May 18, 1959
  - Leib, Samuel F. (2), Jan. 4, 1955, Jan. 19, 1955
  - Leigh, L. P. (3), Mar. 27, 1958, Nov. 17, 1958, Nov. 24, 1958
  - Le Sage, Herbert A. (2), Oct. 29, 1966
  - Lewis, C. S. (1), Mar. 17, 1961
  - Lewis, Fulton (1), May 14, 1951
  - Lewis, Haller (4), Jan. 4, 1957, Jan. 4, 1957, Jan. 30, 1957, July 31, 1957
  - Lewis, Hobart (27), 1954-1959
    Dates of letters: Aug. 12, 1954, Sept. 7, 1956, Sept. 13, 1956, Sept. 20, 1956, Oct. 1, 1956, Nov. 1, 1956, Dec. 7, 1956, Jan. 17, 1957, Jan. 29, 1957, Feb. 25, 1957, Apr. 4, 1957, Apr. 8, 1957, May 13, 1957, Nov. 18, 1957, Dec. 18, 1957, May 6, 1958, June 5, 1958, July 9, 1958, July 24, 1958, Aug. 6, 1958, Aug. 7, 1958, Aug. 12, 1958, Oct. 21, 1958, Dec. 4, 1958, Mar. 3, 1959, Apr. 22, 1959, July 7, 1959
  - Liebman, Marvin (3), Nov. 27, 1957, Feb. 4, 1958, Jan. 15, 1959
  - Limb, B. C. (1), July 30, 1953
  - Limb, Charles H'. (3), June 19, 1958, Jan. 11, 1960, Jan. 14, 1960
  - Ling, Samuel C. H. (2), Mar. 23, 1956, Apr.2, 1956
  - Link, James (2), Nov. 20, 1959, July 17, 1960
  - Linowitz, Sol M. (6), June 21, 1954, June 28, 1954, Aug. 27, 1954, Jan. 14, 1955, Jan. 25, 1955, Feb. 1, 1955
  - Liter, C. P., to Ralph Wheatley (1), June 19, 1954
  - Livingston, T. R. (1), Mar. 5, 1952
  - Lloyd, Wildon (1), Mar. 3, 1953
  - Lockmiller, G. F. (1), Aug. 9, 1954
  - Loeb, William, to Alice Widener (1), Sept. 30,1955
  - Loeb, William (1), Oct. 28, 1955
  - Logan, James H. (1), Feb. 10, 1959
  - Lombard, Mary 0. (14), Aug. 5, 1955, Aug. 31, 1955, Sept. 14, 1955, Sept. 28, 1955, Sept. 21, 1956, Oct. 4, 1956, Dec. 4, 1956, Apr. 23, 1957, June 18, 1957, June 25, 1957, July 10, 1957, July 31, 1957, Aug. 15, 1957, Aug. 22, 1957
  - Lommen, David (1), Dec. 30, 1964
  - London, Robert P. (1), Mar. 10, 1953
  - Long, Hwa S. (1), Jan. 29, 1959
  - Loomis, Philip LeR. (1), Jan. 6, 1953
  - Lovejoy, Philip (2), Nov. 6, 1956, Dec. 2, 1956
  - Lowry, Charles W., to Spadea, Dave Schaffnit, DeWitt Wallace, and William B. Spofford (4), Sept. 4, 1956, Oct. 15, 1956, Jan. 22, 1957, n.d.
  - Lowry, Charles W. (6), Sept. 25, 1956, Nov. 30, 1956, Jan. 9, 1957, Jan. 14, 1957, Mar. 21, 1957, June 28, 1957
  - Lu, Lowell (1), Jan. 26, 1959
  - Lucaf, Janet (1), Mar. 16, 1960
  - Lutz, Lenore and Dexter (1), Oct. 6, 1952
  - Lyman, Carson F., to Robert Keedick (1), Feb. 10, 1955
  - Lyman, Charles J. (1), May 13, 1955
  - MacArthur, Jean B. (4), Mar. 14, 1956, Oct. 4, 1956, Feb. 26, 1957, Mar. 20, 1958
  - MacCallam. Lucile (1), Apr. 8, 1961
  - MacDonald, Kenneth (1), Jan. 20, 1954
  - MacKenzie, Charles A. (2), Aug. 21, 1959, Aug. 26, 1959
  - Main, Frank H. (1), Feb. 20, 1960
  - Maldonado, Fernando (1), Dec. 28, 1960
  - Malik, M. B. K. (6), Dec. 3, 1959, Dec. 15, 1959, Dec. 19, 1959, n.d.
  - Mandel, Benjamin (2), Mar. 18, 1957, June 3, 1957
  - Maness, David, to Robert Keedick (1), Feb. 7, 1955
  - Mann, Marilyn (1), July 29, 1959
  - Marshall, A. F. (1), Feb. 12, 1954
  - Martens, Marlys (1), Jan. 9, 1962
  - Masdoeki, Iin (1), Jan. 14, 1960
  - Massock, Linda (1), Apr. 28, 1957
  - Mathis, R..L. (1), Sept. 30, 1960
  - Matthews, Ralph (1), May 26, 1952
  - Matz, Marjorie (1), Mar. 13, 1961
  - Mauff, Elizabeth (2), Oct. 1, 1957, Nov. 26, 1958
  - Maynard, G. E., to Agnes Sanford, and Norman K. Elliott (2), Apr. 14, 1956, May 18 1956
  - Maynard, G. E. (2), Mar. 28, 1956, Apr. 14, 1956
  - McAlister, Mike (1), Feb. 8, 1966
  - McCahon, William H. (1), Aug. 23, 1960
  - McCaniles, H. A. (1), May 30, 1955
  - McCann, Thomas P. (5), May 31, 1963, June 14, 1963, June 18, 1963, July 15, 1963, Aug. 14, 1963
  - McCarley, Trimmier (1), May 21, 1952
  - McCartly, Fred (1), Dec. 16, 1965
  - McDonald, James M. (1), May 2, 1963
  - McEachern, Margaret (1), May 15, 1958
  - McFadden, Faith (6), May 27, 1959, June 10, 1959, July 3, 1959, July 15, 1959, July 23, 1959, Aug. 10, 1959
    7
  - McGregor, O. E. (1), Mar. 23, 1954
  - McIntyre, Donald K. (1), July 28, 1959
  - McIntyre, F. D. (1), n.d.
  - McMullen, John S. (1), Mar. 27, 1958
  - McNair, Clyde (3), June 11, 1957, Mar. 20, 1959, n.d.
  - McNally, Jean (1), Feb. 17, 1959
  - McNeil, Donald S (1), Mar. 3, 1953
  - Meeker, Marjorie S. (4), Oct. 30, 1957, June 9, 1959, June 29, 1959, Dec. 18, 1959
  - Meglaughlin, B. F., to Alice Windener (1), Nov. 28, 1956
  - Meisenhelder, Edmund W. (1), Oct. 28, 1959
  - Meissner, Fredrik (1), July 22, 1960
  - Mejia, Augusto L. (1), May 31, 1963
  - Mendheim, Beverly-; (1), Apr, 6, 1962
  - Meneses, Walfrido R. (1), July 22, 1959
  - Menjou, Aldolphe, to Counter attach (1), Mar. 24, 1955
  - Mensah, R. O. (1), Mar. 4, 1958
  - Mercer, Sam N. (3), May 16, 1958, Jan. 14, 1959, Oct. 22, 1959
  - Meredith, Louise (1), Jan. 10, 1957
  - Merk, Thomas (1), May 22, 1962
  - Merwin, Jane (4), Jan. 2, 1959, Dec. 16, 1959, June 28, 1960, July 8, 1960
  - Messenger, Gail R. (1), Aug. 3, 1956
  - Michener, James A. (1), June 20, 1957
  - Miller, Dan S. (2), Nov. 17, 1953, May 17, 1954
  - Miller, Hank (2), July 21, 1956, Sept. 13, 1956
  - Miller, Raymond.W. (1), Apr. 6, 1959
  - Mills, Irene W., to William F. Strube (1), Oct. 12, 1954
  - Mills, R. M. (1), Sept. 15, 1952
  - Mills, V. J. R. (2), Mar. 8, 1956, Mar. 26, 1965
  - Mingo, Larry (1), Mar. 13, 1963
  - Minsky, Louis (2), Aug. 16, 1957, Aug. 26, 1957
  - Miscione, F. Paul (2), June 15, 1964; July 16, 1964
  - Mitchell, James R. (1), Feb. 8, 1966
  - Moench, Ernest (1), Mar. 1, 1954
  - Monroe, L. C., to Miss Reidy (1), Apr. 15, 1955
  - Monroe, Margaret H. (2), Oct. 18, 1960, Nov, 8, 1960
  - Moore, Sam (1), Nov. 3, 1964
  - Morris, George B., to Adron Greene (1), Nov. 13, 1958
  - Morris, George B. (6), Jan. 21, 1959; Feb. 6, 1959, Feb. 19, 1959, Sept. 14, 1959, Jan. 9, 1962, Jan. 21, 1963
  - Moore, Goerge W. (1), n.d.
  - Morrison, W. B. (2), Oct. 4, 1955, Nov. 3, 1955
  - Morrow, Glenn C., to Elizabeth Schenk (1), Feb. 16, 1953
  - Morse, F. Whitton, to Michael Schlar, Galen Drake, Richard Lewine, Steve Fleichman, Allen Sherman, and Herb Sanford (6), Oct. 1, 1956, Oct. 4, 1956
  - Morton, Margaret E. (1), Oct. 25, 1959
  - Moss, Charles, to James V. Spadea (1), Aug. 1, 1953
  - Moulton, Sumner (1), July 6, 1955
  - Mount, Eloise E., to Elizabeth Schenk (1), Apr. 10, 1956
  - Mount, Eloise E. (1), Apr. 9,.1956
  - Muller, H. J. (1), Mar. 20, 1951
  - Munro, N. S. (1), Jan. 29, 1963
  - Murphy, Arthur R. (5), June 26, 1959, July 6, 1959, Jan. 5, 1961, Jan. 27, 1961, Mar. 7, 1961
  - Murphy, Mary K. (1), June 3, 1964
  - Murphy, U. G. (3), Dec. 24, 1956, Jan. 18, 1957, Feb. 1, 1957
  - Murray, Anna E. (1), Nov. 25, 1953
  - Mustoe, Janice (2), Aug. 13, 1966, Oct. 10, 1966
  - Mutsu, Ian (4), July 2, 1958, Aug. 8, 1958, Sept. 10, 1958, n.d.
  - Myers, Eve E. (1), n.d.
  - Myers, Henry M. (1), Apr. 5, 1957
  - Myklebust, A. S., to Miss Reidy (1), Dec. 2, 1959
  - Naegele, J. Arthur (1), Nov. 28, 1965
  - Nan-Ju, Wu (2), Jan. 8, 1955, Mar. 15, 1955
  - Napoli, Louise (2), Sept. 14, 1955, Nov. 9, 1955
  - Nash, E. T. (1), Nov. 13, 1958
  - Naughton, Thomas J., to Mary Greene (1), Feb. 24, 1954
  - Neel, W. H. (1), May 16, 1953
  - Neighbors, Lois L,., to Miss Reidy and Keedick Lecture (2), Oct. 19, 1959, Dec. 3, 1959
  - Neighbors, Lois L. (1), Oct. 30, 1959
  - Nelson, Christine A., to Robert Keedick (1), Jan. 31, 1959
  - Nelson, Christine A. (2), Jan. 12, 1959, Jan. 30, 1959
  - Nelson, Frederic, to U. G. Murphy (1), Jan. 19, 1957
  - Nelgon, Frederic (3), Nov. 2, 1956, Apr. 15, 1958, Sept. 12, 1961
  - Neuffer, Frank R. (2), Nov. 8, 1954, Nov, 22, 1954
  - Newhart, Ellwood H. (1), Oct. 28, 1959
  - Niccolls, S. A. (1), July 14, 1959
  - Nichols, Jack W. (2), June 24, 1959, Sept. 24, 1959
  - Nicholson, B. M. (1), Aug. lo, 1962
  - Nicholson, Rodney A. (1), July 2, 1959
  - Nickell, Paulena, to Keedick Lecture (1), Dec. 3, 1959
  - Nierenberg, Harry H. (2), Jan. 1, 1960, n.d.
  - Nirodi, Hira (2), Oct. 16, 1959, Nov, 4, 1959
  - Nisbet, Ulric, to Howard Clark (1), Apr. 22, 1955
  - Nitske, Betty L. (1), Oct. 24, 1960
  - Nixon, Richard, to James V. Spadea and Charles W. Lowry (2), Feb. 17, 1956, Nov. 7, 1965
  - Noble, Charles M. (1), Apr. 21, 1954
  - Nonnenmacher, Nicholas T. (2), Apr. 8, 1955, Oct. 29, 1956
  - Nordburg, William S., to L. F. Harza (1), May 15, 1952
  - Norton, Florence (2), May 28, 1954, June 21, 1954
  - O'Conor, Herbert R. (1), Apr. 27, 1955
  - Ogburn, Charlton, to O. E. McGregor (1), Mar. 22, 1954
  - Oh, Chae Kyung (2), June 21, 1958, n.d.
  - Ohly, Robert G. (1), Mar. 13, 1961
  - O'Keefe, Margaret (1), Oct. 8, 1966
  - Oliver, Elizabeth (1), Jan. 21, 1958
  - Oliver, Robert T. (15), Oct. 20, 1953, Nov. 3, 1953, Mar. 27, 1954, Oct. 24, 1955, Nov. 4, 1955, Nov. 25, 1955, Feb. 6, 1956, Feb. 25, 1958, Mar. 11, 1958, Mar. 31, 1958, Apr. 13, 1958, Jan. 23, 1959, Feb. 21, 1959, Apr. 24, 1959
  - Orrell, May (2), May 19, 1954, Feb. 2, 1957
  - Paddock, Mary T. (1), Sept. 20, 1952
  - Paeschke, Charles W., To Keedick Lecture Bureau (2), Mar. 14, 1961
  - Paeschke, Charles W. (2), Mar. 16, 1961, Mar. 31, 1961
  - Pagenhart, Esther (1), Aug. 6, 1952
  - Palmer, Paul, to Lee Keedick (2), Feb. 11, 1955, Apr. 1, 1955
  - Pan American World Airways (1), Nov, 23, 1960
  - Pan-Paa (1), July 17, 1959
  - Panyarachun, Kusa (1), Sept. 13, 1959
  - Parsons, John W. (1), Mar. 21, 1953
  - Parsley, Virginia (1), July 15, 1955
  - Payne, Kenneth W. (1), Sept. 17, 1954
  - Pendall, D. J. (1), Mar. 2, 1959
  - Pennington, Lee R. (1), Aug. 3, 1956
  - Pentlarge, Alice (2), Feb. 29, 1952, Mar. 14, 1952
  - Perdue, LaVerne (1), Oct. 25, 1955
  - Perry, G. O., to James MacPherson (1), Jan. 6, 1956
  - Perry, G. O. (5), Aug. 29, 1956, Dec. 7, 1957, Jan. 20, 1958, Aug. 21, 1960, Oct. 17, 1960
  - Perryman, Sally (1), Feb. 23, 1960
  - Peters, Peggy (1), Sept. 21, 1962
  - Peterson, E. Denmarest (6), Feb. 28, 1960, Mar. 2, 1960, Mar. 8, 1960, Apr. 15, 1960, Aug. 5, 1960, n.d.
  - Peterson, Ed R., to John Day Co. (1), Apr. 23, 1962
  - Petzoldt, W. A. (1), n.d.
  - Phelps, George (1), June 6, 1955
  - Phelps, Jewell (1), Jan. 27, 1955
  - Phillips, T. 0. (1), Aug. 26, 1957
  - Pickett, Louis L. (1), Oct. 31, 1952
  - Pilger, Elsa R. (2), Aug. 6, 1959, Dec. 5, 1959
  - Pipes, Richard L. (1), Mar. 26, 1964
  - Plake, F. Marvin, to V. P. T. S., T. N. N. and William Shaver and Charles Pearcy (2), June 19, 1956, Nov. 1, 1956
  - Plake, Marvin (11), Aug. 13, 1956, Aug. 28, 1956, Oct. 6, 1956, Dec. 24, 1956, Feb. 18, 1957, Aug. 13, 1957, Jan. 13, 1960, Mar. 11, 1960, Apr. 7, 1960, June 15, 1960, July 23, 1960
  - Playfair, Charles S. (1), Dec. 10, 1957
  - Plumb, Florence J. (1), Apr. 26, 1953
  - Poey, Barbara M. (5), June 15, 1961, July 21, 1961, Jan. 8, 1962, Feb, 15, 1962, Nov. 2, 1962
  - Poling, Daniel A., to Mr. Stewart, Hall, Wilson, Madame Chiang Kai-shek, Ben Hibbs, Robert Keedick, and Richard Walsh (6), Feb. 15, 1954, Feb. 15, 1954, Nov. 1, 1954, July 8, 1955, July 18, 1955, Nov, 22, 1955
  - Poling, Daniel A. (23), 1953-1958
    Dates of letters: June 4, 1953, June 12, 1953, Nov. 20, 1953, Jan. 26, 1954, Feb. 15, 1954, Nov. 1, 1954, Nov. 3, 1954, Nov. 17, 1954, Feb. 18, 1955, Mar. 9, 1955, July 11, 1955, July 19, 1955, Sept. 8, 1955, Nov, 22, 1955, Feb. 7, 1956, Apr. 11, 1956, Apr. 18, 1956, May 17, 1956, Aug. 30, 1956, Dec. 5, 1956, Jan. 28, 1957, Feb. 18, 1958, n.d., n.d.
  - Polk, Fay (2), Oct. 23, 1957, Nov. 15, 1957
  - Porter, R. H., to R. R. Vance (2), Mar. 9, 1959, Mar. 25, 1959
  - Porter, R. H. (7), Jan. 19, 1959, Feb. 20, 1959, Feb. 27, 1959, Mar. 9, 1959, Mar. 25, 1959, Apr. 6, 1959, Apr. 13, 1959
  - Potter, Russell (5), Jan. 11, 1951, Jan. 17, 1951, Feb. 2, 1951, Feb. 7, 1951, May 15, 1951
  - Powell, Jane (1), Mar. 21, 1955
  - Pratt, Tony (1), n.d.
  - Price, Harry (1), n.d.
  - Price, Ruth A. (1), June 21, 1956
  - Prince, Walter j. to Miki Sawada (1), Aug. 25, 1951
  - Pritchard, Lucette M. (1), June 25, 1965
  - Purcell, Kathleen, to Robert Keedick (1), Nov. 7, 1957
  - Purcell, Kathleen (1), Jan. 14, 1959
  - Putnam, Rufus A., to Manion J. Prittchard (1), Apr. 25, 1957
  - Pyle, W. Walter (1), June 24, 1954
  - Qadir, Anees Riaz (2), Dec. 16, 1959, n.d.
  - Quackenbush, Helen, (1), Aug. 5, 1952
  - Rado, Charles (1), Feb. 10, 1959
  - Rae, William E. (1), Oct. 20, 1953
  - Ragsdale, C. D., to Amarillo Daily News (1), Feb. 11, 1953
  - Ragsdale, J. L. (1), May 16, 1957
  - Ramke, Thomas F. (1), May 7, 1954
  - Raney, William (1), Mar. 27, 1953
  - Rappaport, Albert (2), n.d.
  - Raum, H. E. (1), n.d.
  - Raymond, Will (2), July 4, 1960, July 19, 1960
  - Redden, Joseph P., to Loretta Reidy (1), Feb. 2, 1955
  - Reed, Forrest F., to George H. Barnes (1), Feb. 6, 1957
  - Reed, Forrest F.. (3), Dec. 7, 1956, Feb. 6, 1960, June 15, 1960
  - Rees, Betty (1), July 4, 1959
  - Regal, Charles (1), Jan. 7, 1963
  - Regnery, Henry, to Ruth Aley, Jaclb Riis, L. H. Hunt, Hanford McNader, William T. Gossett, Alfred Kolberg, Walter, Trohon, Daniel Smoot, Frances G. Knight, Ruth Shipley, M. P. Goodfellow, DeWitt.Wallace, and "Bookseller" (15), Apr. 29, 1952, May 6, 1952, May 27, 1952, Oct. 8, 1952, Oct. 23, 1952, Dec. 22, 1952, July 20, 1953, July 22, 1953, July 28, 1953, Feb. 15, 1955, Feb. 21, 1955
  - Regnery, Henry (70), 1952-1964